$SK_CONTINUE	Continue
$SK_ASCENDED{}	You have ascended to level {}
$SK_LEVEL2	You realize that all your life you have been coasting along as if you were in a dream. Suddenly, facing the trials of the last few days, you have come alive.
$SK_LEVEL3	You realize that you are catching on to the secret of success. It's just a matter of concentration.
$SK_LEVEL4	It's all suddenly obvious to you. You just have to concentrate. All the energy and time you've wasted -- it's a sin. But without the experience you've gained, taking risks, taking responsibility for failure, how could you have understood?
$SK_LEVEL5	Everything you do is just a bit easier, more instinctive, more satisfying. It is as though you had suddenly developed keen senses and instincts.
$SK_LEVEL6	You sense yourself more aware, more open to new ideas. You've learned a lot about Morrowind. It's hard to believe how ignorant you were -- but now you have so much more to learn.
$SK_LEVEL7	You resolve to continue pushing yourself. Perhaps there's more to you than you thought.
$SK_LEVEL8	The secret does seem to be hard work, yes, but it's also a kind of blind passion, an inspiration.
$SK_LEVEL9	Everything you do is just a bit easier, more instinctive, more satisfying. It is as though you had suddenly developed keen senses and instincts.
$SK_LEVEL10	You woke today with a new sense of purpose. You're no longer afraid of failure. Failure is just an opportunity to learn something new.
$SK_LEVEL11	Being smart doesn't hurt. And a little luck now and then is nice. But the key is patience and hard work. And when it pays off, it's SWEET!
$SK_LEVEL12	You can't believe how easy it is. You just have to go -- a little crazy. And then, suddenly, it all makes sense, and everything you do turns to gold.
$SK_LEVEL13	It's the most amazing thing. Yesterday it was hard, and today it is easy. Just a good night's sleep, and yesterday's mysteries are today's masteries.
$SK_LEVEL14	Today you wake up, full of energy and ideas, and you know, somehow, that overnight everything has changed. What a difference a day makes.
$SK_LEVEL15	Today you suddenly realized the life you've been living, the punishment your body has taken -- there are limits to what the body can do, and perhaps you have reached them. You've wondered what it is like to grow old. Well, now you know.
$SK_LEVEL16	You've been trying too hard, thinking too much. Relax. Trust your instincts. Just be yourself. Do the little things, and the big things take care of themselves.
$SK_LEVEL17	Life isn't over. You can still get smarter, or cleverer, or more experienced, or meaner -- but your body and soul just aren't going to get any younger.
$SK_LEVEL18	The challenge now is to stay at the peak as long as you can. You may be as strong today as any mortal who has ever walked the earth, but there's always someone younger, a new challenger.
$SK_LEVEL19	You're really good. Maybe the best. And that's why it's so hard to get better. But you just keep trying, because that's the way you are.
$SK_LEVEL20	You'll never be better than you are today. If you are lucky, by superhuman effort, you can avoid slipping backwards for a while. But sooner or later, you're going to lose a step, or drop a beat, or miss a detail -- and you'll be gone forever.
$SK_LEVELDEFAULT	The results of hard work and dedication always look like luck to saps. But you know you've earned every ounce of your success.
$------------birthsignstuff	----------------------
$the	The
$lover	LOVER
$apprentice	APPRENTICE
$lord	LORD
$ritual	RITUAL
$atronach	ATRONACH
$lady	LADY
$mage	MAGE
$serpent	SERPENT
$shadow	SHADOW
$steed	STEED
$thief	THIEF
$tower	TOWER
$warrior	WARRIOR
$apprentice_DESC	The Apprentice is one of the charges of the Mage, and its season is Sun's Height. Those born under the sign of the Apprentice have much more magicka, but are more vulnerable to magick as well.
$apprentice_AB0_NAME	Elfborn
$apprentice_AB0_DESC	Fortify Magicka 1.5x
$apprentice_AB1_NAME	Elfborn
$apprentice_AB1_DESC	Weakness to Magicka 50% on Self
$atronach_DESC	The Atronach is one of the Mage's charges and its season is Sun's Dusk. Those born under this sign are natural sorcerers who frequently absorb hostile spells and possess deep reserves of magicka, but they cannot regenerate magicka naturally.
$atronach_AB0_NAME	Wombburn
$atronach_AB0_DESC	Fortify Magicka 2.0x
$atronach_AB1_NAME	Wombburn
$atronach_AB1_DESC	Spell Absorption 50% on Self
$atronach_AB2_NAME	Wombburn
$atronach_AB2_DESC	No Magicka Regen
$ritual_DESC	The Ritual is one of the Mage's charges and its season is Morning Star. Those born under this sign carry the Divine's blessing. They can turn the undead, their spells are more powerful against them, and they have the ability to greatly restore their health and magicka once each day.
$ritual_AB0_NAME	Arkay's Grace
$ritual_AB0_DESC	All spells are 25% more powerful vs. undead
$ritual_AB1_NAME	Blessed Ward
$ritual_AB1_DESC	Turn Undead 100 points (level 30?) for 30 seconds.
$ritual_AB2_NAME	Mara's Grace
$ritual_AB2_DESC	Restore Health and Magicka 100pts
$mage_DESC	The Mage is a guardian constellation whose season is Rain's Hand when magicka was first used by men. Those born under the Mage  are often talented, arrogant, and absent-minded. They have more magicka than others, and can intensify the power of their spells at the cost of greater magicka drain.
$mage_AB0_NAME	Fay
$mage_AB0_DESC	Fortify Magicka 0.5x
$mage_AB1_NAME	Fay
$mage_AB1_DESC	Spells are 25% more powerful for 30 seconds but cost 10% more magicka
$lady_DESC	The Lady is one of the Warrior's charges and her season is Hearthfire. Those born under the sign of the Lady are beloved and possess great fortitude.
$lady_AB0_NAME	Lady's Favor
$lady_AB0_DESC	Fortify Personality 25 Points
$lady_AB1_NAME	Lady's Grace
$lady_AB1_DESC	Fortify Endurance 25 Points
$lord_DESC	The Lord is one of the Warrior's charges. During his season of First Seed he oversees planting over all Tamriel. Those born under the sign of the Lord are stronger and can work longer than those born under other signs, but they are more suceptible to fire.
$lord_AB0_NAME	Blood of the North
$lord_AB0_DESC	Fortify Strength 25 Points
$lord_AB1_NAME	Blood of the North
$lord_AB1_DESC	Fortify Endurance 25 Points
$lord_AB2_NAME	Trollkin
$lord_AB2_DESC	Weakness to Fire 100%
$steed_DESC	The Steed is one of the Warrior's charges, and its season is Mid Year. Those born under the sign of the Steed are impatient and always hurrying from one place to another. They can also make their blows in battle more swift, though more tiring.
$steed_AB0_NAME	
$steed_AB0_DESC	Fortify Speed 25 Points on Self
$steed_AB1_NAME	
$steed_AB1_DESC	Weapon speed increased 20%, but lose 2 stamina/sec for 30 seconds
$warrior_DESC	The Warrior is a guardian constellation. His season is Last Seed when his strength is needed for the harvest. Those born under this sign are short-tempered and can sometimes strike foes with devistating force.
$warrior_AB0_NAME	
$warrior_AB0_DESC	All physical attacks have a 10% chance of doing double damage
$serpent_DESC	The Serpent wanders the sky threating other constellations and has no set season. Those born under this sign are the most blessed and the most cursed on Tamriel. Their luck is strong, but they are vulnerable to poison, and they may inflict a bite on others that poisions them both. Once each day, they may instantly cure themselves of poison.
$serpent_AB0_NAME	Star-Curse
$serpent_AB0_DESC	Fortify Luck 25 points
$serpent_AB1_NAME	Star-Curse
$serpent_AB1_DESC	Weakness to Poison 100% on self
$serpent_AB2_NAME	Snake's Bite
$serpent_AB2_DESC	Poison on touch 3 points & self 1 points for 30 seconds
$serpent_AB3_NAME	Snake Spell
$serpent_AB3_DESC	Cure posion
$lover_DESC	The Lover is one of the Thief's charges and her season is Sun's Dawn. Those born under the sign of the Lover are graceful and passionate. Though it is exhausting they can sometimes paralyze others with the touch of their lips.
$lover_AB0_NAME	Mooncalf
$lover_AB0_DESC	Fortify Agility 25 points on self
$lover_AB1_NAME	Lover's Kiss
$lover_AB1_DESC	Paralyze 60 Seconds on Touch, Damage Fatigue 200 Points on Self
$shadow_DESC	The Shadow is a charge of the Thief, and his season is Second Seed. The Shadow grants those born under the sign the ability to better hide in shadows, though the effort is tiring, and once each day they may render themselves invisible for a time.
$shadow_AB0_NAME	Fingernail Moon
$shadow_AB0_DESC	20% harder to detect & drains 2 stamina/sec for the next 30 seconds
$shadow_AB1_NAME	Moonshadow
$shadow_AB1_DESC	Invisibility for 60 Seconds on Self
$tower_DESC	The Tower is one of the Thief's charges and its season is Frostfall. Those born under the sign of the Tower have a knack for avoiding others when they wish to hide and once each day they can open difficult locks and reflect some blows back at any who attack them.
$tower_AB0_NAME	The Master's Hands
$tower_AB0_DESC	For 15 seconds, detect life 200ft & locks are 20% easier to pick
$tower_AB1_NAME	Tower Key
$tower_AB1_DESC	Open Adept Lock [50 Points] on Target
$tower_AB2_NAME	Tower Warden
$tower_AB2_DESC	Reflect Damage 5% for 120 Seconds on Self
$thief_DESC	The Thief is a guardian constellation, and its season is the darkest month of Evening Star. Those born under the sign of the Thief are not typically thieves, though they take risks more often and only rarely come to harm. They do run out of luck eventually, however, and often don't live as long as those born under other signs.
$thief_AB0_NAME	Akiviri Danger-Sense
$thief_AB0_DESC	Sanctuary 10 points
$ABILITY	ABILITY
$LESSER_POWER	LESSER POWER
$GREATER_POWER	GREATER POWER
$Proceed	Proceed
$BirthsignMenuTitle	What is your Birthsign?
$BirthsignMenuTips	Blah blah brah bruh --- ABILITIES are permanent effects, LESSER POWERs can be used every 2 minutes, and GREATER POWERs can be used once a day. Birthsigns cannot be changed later.
$------------endbirthsignstuff	----------------------
$Medium	Medium
$MediumArmor	Medium Armor
$Legend	Legend
$MagesGuild	Mage's Guild
$COMBAT	COMBAT
$MAGIC	Magic
$CLASS	CLASS
$STEALTH	STEALTH
$WEREWOLF	WEREWOLF
$VAMPIRE	VAMPIRE
$ATTRIBUTES	ATTRIBUTES
$STRENGTH	STRENGTH
$INTELLIGENCE	INTELLIGENCE
$WILLPOWER	WILLPOWER
$ENDURANCE	ENDURANCE
$AGILITY	AGILITY
$SPEED	SPEED
$PERSONALITY	PERSONALITY
$LUCK	LUCK
$BOUNTY	BOUNTY
$REPUTATION	REPUTATION
$RENOWN	RENOWN
$Description	Description
$UNLOCKS	UNLOCKS
$REQUIRES	REQUIRES
$BIRTHSIGN:	BIRTHSIGN:
$SPECIALIZATION:	SPECIALIZATION:
$MAJOR ATTRIBUTES:	MAJOR ATTRIBUTES:
$MAJOR SKILLS:	MAJOR SKILLS:
$FACTIONS	FACTIONS
$FACTIONS	FACTIONS
$MYSTICISM CATEGORY	MYSTICISM
$Mysticism School	Mysticism
$War Axe	War Axe
$Battleaxe	Battleaxe
$Mace	Mace
$Club	Club
$Warhammer	Warhammer
$Longsword	Longsword
$Broadsword	Broadsword
$Katana	Katana
$Saber	Saber
$Claymore	Claymore
$Dai-Katana	Dai-Katana
$Bow	Bow
$Crossbow	Crossbow
$Quarterstaff	Quarterstaff
$Spear	Spear
$Halberd	Halberd
$Dagger	Dagger
$Tanto	Tanto
$Shortsword	Shortsword
$Wakizashi	Wakizashi
$Left Hand	Left Hand
$Right Hand	Right Hand
$Right Pauldron	Right Shoulder
$Left Pauldron	Left Shoulder
$Greaves	Legs
$Repair	Repair Tool
$Apparatus	Apparatus
$CRITDMG	CRIT DMG.
$CRTPCT	CRIT %
$SPEED	SPEED
$REACH	REACH
$STAGGER	STAGGER
$ARMORM	ARMOR BYPASS
$ESS_DEATH_MESSAGE	With this character's death, the thread of prophecy is severed. Load a saved game to restore the weave of fate, or persist in the doomed world you have created.
$ESS_DEATH_SAVE	Load a   Save
$ESS_DEATH_CONT	Continue Anyway
$RingEquipLeft	Equip to Left Hand
$RingEquipRight	Equip to Right Hand
$ThrowingKnife	Throwing Knife
$ThrowingDart	Throwing Dart
$ThrowingStar	Throwing Star
$Bomb	Bomb
$ToggleEffects	Effects
$ToggleDescription	Description
